and say "a-ha" again?
(Leonard:)I'm sorry, Sheldon.
I should've told you I was back.
(Leonard:)I just wanted to have
a couple days alone with Penny.
(Sheldon:)Oh, no, I should apologize.
(Sheldon:)I never realized to what extent
our friendship was a burden to you.
(Leonard:)That is not fair.
(Leonard:)I complain about what a burden it is
at least once a month.
Oh, no, no, Iefs not sugarcoat this.
You find me tinicky,
pedantic and annoying.
(Penny:)No, he doesn't.
(Leonard:)I actually have used
those exact words before.
(Leonard:)In that order.
(Sheldon:)Well, Leonard,
I think it's high time
(Sheldon:)you and I address
the "tweepadock" in the room.
(Leonard:)-The what?
-Amy?
(Amy:)-Please leave me out of this.
-Fine.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, there's no need for you
to pretend to like me anymore.
(Leonard:)-Come on, I said I was sorry.
-No, no, you save your apologies
(Sheldon:)for after you've had
disappointing coitus with Penny.